https://waccamawcf.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This website is owned and operated by Waccamaw Community Foundation. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity, and security of personal information entrusted to us. Your right to privacy is very important to us. We recognize that providing Waccamaw Community Foundation with your personal information is an act of trust. The following Privacy Policy was developed to assure you that we take seriously our responsibility to protect customer information and use it only in ways that are consistent with your wishes.
Our Policy
On our site we don’t collect personally identifiable information about individuals unless they knowingly provide it to us. If you only want to browse and learn about our services, programs, and benefits, we invite you to do so. As a casual, unregistered visitor to our site, we’ll recognize your internet service provider but not your e-mail address or any other personal or system information.
If you are a Foundation donor and want to access information about your fund, it will be necessary for you to provide personally identifiable information. This may include your name, address, e-mail address, and phone number. Any information you provide will be downloaded from the web server and maintained in a secure system. Though this functionality does not yet exist, we hope to offer this service to our donors in the near future.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting changes on this page. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of those changes.
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
